softwarert.com 2017-07-30

# Privacy | Software RT

### Privacy Policy

Welcome to www.softwarert.com website. www.softwarert.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. This Privacy Policy discloses how we collect and use information, and the choices that you can make about the way we collect and use your information. We understand that your trust depends on how we respect your privacy and how we safeguard information you provide us. We want you to feel comfortable using our website, products, and services and encourage you to read this Privacy Policy, detailing the online practices for www.softwarert.com (“Software RT”).

This Privacy Policy applies to all the products and software published, advertised, promoted through www.softwarert.com.

By accessing and using www.softwarert.com or providing any information requested, you agree to accept the terms of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the site.

**What Information We Collect**

When you place an order on our website, your full name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card number, and credit card expiration date will be required. The information is used to complete the transaction and help us provide better support and services to you.

**How Customers’ Information Protected**

Software RT uses secure server hosted by SWREG, Regnow and other 3rd party credit card processors that encrypt all the customer’s personal information before it is sent to us, including name, address, credit card number, credit card expiration date, etc. Encryption works to prevent any malicious use of your personal information. Your credit card information is only used for online transition.

**Informed Consent**

Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy, Software RT will not disclose personally identifiable information to companies not owned by us who want to market products or services to you without your prior informed consent.

**Third-party AD Serving**

We may use third-party advertising companies， like Google Adsense, to serve ads when you visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visit to www.softwarert.com in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to the softwarert.com website, our third-party advertising companies may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

**About COOKIES**

To enhance your experience with our website, many of our web pages use “cookies.” Cookies themselves do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information, they are text files we place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings. Cookies cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.

You can choose to disable the cookies by changing your Internet browser settings. However, by doing so, you may not have full access to all the web pages.

**Our Commitment to Security**

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and prevent unauthorized access, to maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about this www.softwarert.com Privacy Policy or its implementation please contact us via email. Our email following address can be found at [the contact page here](https://www.softwarert.com/contact/).
